

NGUYEN VAN A

MARKETING MANAGER

Male

May 19, 1992

♥ Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and us because it is so versatile. Select how many paragra of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

EDUCATION



FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY

major. Donate Bitcoin: 16UQLq1HZ3CNwhvgrarV6pM administration

m Sep 2007 - Present

FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

EXPERIENCE



Sep 2007 - Present

CVPRO JSC

Sale Executive

Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult quan tâm đến nó. Đoạn 1.10.32 và 1.10.33 trong cuốn "De Finibus Bonorum et Mal and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

CVPRO JSC

Sale Executive

Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and
- Assist to êm vào những câu hài hước hay thông tục). Nó đến từ goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

ACTIVITIES



Sep 2003 - 2007

CVPRO JSC

Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer es pains to avoid worse pains." $\label{eq:policy} \textbf{help@lipsum.com\ Privacy\ Policy\cdot Do\ Not\ Sell\ My\ Personal\ Info'\ queries\ via\ phone\ and\ email.}$
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

CERTIFICATIONS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2013 - 2014

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US ng agile frameworks to provide a

REFERENCES



NGUYEN VAN BINH

director of cvpro jsc

SKILLS





INTERESTS



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt the filler text has been used for cen and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities